{
    "subject": "resource/Namma_Metro",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/homepage",
    "object": "http://bmrc.co.in/",
    "human_readable": "The homepage of Namma Metro is http://bmrc.co.in/.`}",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.918716549873352,
            "question": "What is the URL of the Namma Metro homepage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8847571611404419,
            "question": "Is there an official website for Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8091857433319092,
            "question": "What is the web address of the Namma Metro website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7439783215522766,
            "question": "How can you access information about Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7128224968910217,
            "question": "Where can you find information about Namma Metro online?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.710951566696167,
            "question": "Can you find information about Namma Metro on the internet?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6189780831336975,
            "question": "Where would you go online to learn about Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5722382068634033,
            "question": "Which organization manages Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5649764537811279,
            "question": "Does Namma Metro have an online presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.170770063996315,
            "question": "What is the web address of the Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation website?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The homepage of Namma Metro is http://bmrc.co.in/.`}",
            "html": "dbpedia_6374_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Namma Metro have an online presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6374_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which organization manages Namma Metro?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6374_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where would you go online to learn about Namma Metro?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6374_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6374_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nLet me explain why: None of the provided text documents mention  a homepage URL for Namma Metro. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I will evaluate whether the triple \"The homepage of Namma Metro is http://bmrc.co.in/\" is correct or not.\n\nAfter analyzing the documents, I found that there is no explicit mention of the homepage URL in any of the text. However, in one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6374/re-ranker-msmarco/45.txt), it mentions \"Partner Websites: www.rblbank.com\" and another website \"help@ongo.co.in\" but not the homepage URL of Namma Metro.\n\nTherefore, I conclude that the triple is incorrect because there is no information in the provided context to support the claim that the homepage of Namma Metro is http://bmrc.co.in/. \n\nThe final answer is: \n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents contain information related to the homepage of Namma Metro being \"http://bmrc.co.in/\". Therefore, the query cannot be confirmed as correct based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}